testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Who's protecting me?
Me
testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
What am I
protecting?
fromis_9
Why?
Flovers
which music show was your favorite this time?
No I mean
yesterday
when we went to the radio that
camera director
I saw him. The Music Bank one
That director
really
paid a lot of attention to us
Since about two weeks ago
he was thinking hard about how to capture the colors
really
thinking hard about it
he was thinking hard about how to capture the colors
really
thinking hard about it
and doing all this
he told me
But
if you look at the camera work doesn't it have a lot of affection in it? He said he's a Flover
Right?
So during the White Longing era and
this time too
it totally has
some affection in it
The one-take
there
the director who filmed that put his heart into it
It's full of it
I wonder who his bias is?
I don't remember but I think he told me
I think it was Hayoung unnie
No
during our Supersonic
era
the director too
the 2nd camera director
right?
I don't remember but 2 years ago
it wasn't me anyway
Yeah anyway
they filmed us
really beautifully so
Music Core too
really
the FD and
everyone really took care of us
This time all the music shows really paid a lot of attention to us
For Inkigayo
the writer
Jiho
got the Park Jiwoo buff so
I really have good friends
But this time Inkigayo gave us all face cams
so it was so
Right I was going to film with Wooah's
Wooyeon
With Wooah's Wooyeon too
I was originally going to film it yesterday or the day before
but after the fansign
Wooyeon also had a fansign
and after it ended
it was too late so
we decided to keep it. My jewel box
is it okay to reveal it like this?
My jewels
Park Jiwoo
Park Jiwoo that girl
ah she said she'd film it for me
seriously
Next time we meet
we're going to meet but
I have to convince her next time we meet
seriously
I'll give you an easy one
You don't even have to dance
Ah I'm telling you you don't have to dance. Really
It's fine
Your dancing
is a bit
Ah you're cute
You have to do it like this
Do it the Eui-jin version
It's 1 minute before
Look
Our
Jiwon unnie
please look at my ticket
From the start
smoothly
And
etiquette is important guys
Make sure
our Flovers
become known as people who
follow etiquette well
Got it?
When you go see the play
etiquette
manners
I'm not saying you have to watch like a statue
just follow
basic etiquette. We have to follow etiquette when watching movies too
Our Flovers
Flovers who are seeing it for the first time
keep your
manners
Flovers who are seeing it for the first time
Don't scream
manners
As long as you don't bother others
that's etiquette
Don't move your body around too much
Like this
you shouldn't do that
we are adults so
like adults
yeah
you can sit still and watch
for 2 or 3 hours right?
We can do at least that much since we're adults
And even if you aren't adults
uh
you aren't babies
Yeah
Born in 2012?
How old are you if you were born in 2012?
Born in 2012
how old is that?
Are they nine years
younger than me?
15 years old
Ah if you're 15
you're all grown up
I started working
when I was 15
uh
when I started my social life
You're all grown up
You should know how to do that much
I think
elementary schoolers
10 years old
and under
are babies
and after 10 you can think for yourself to some extent
I don't think being young
is an excuse. You are young
You're young
You still
haven't fully grown
and you're young but
you're at an age where
you should follow basic etiquette
So
let's
keep our etiquette
Our
wait
our Jiwon unnie
To make her look even prettier
our fans
please
make her look pretty. Our Jiwon unnie
What's the vibe of my hair right now? It's just my at-home look
Well
it might look like I'm trying to act cute but
I just normally live like this. It's comfortable. Otherwise I have to tie it back completely
and tie it back tight and put a mask on
but
uh
ever since I got medium length hair doing a bun became so uncomfortable
It doesn't tie back smoothly
so I just
pin my bangs up
and tie it like this
doing it like this
when I come out
Let's hang out on live stream until it comes
As Jiwon unnie
go to
M Countdown
she was really pretty right
That red outfit
I told you I requested it
They put the filter
really softly
for us
My skin completely looked like this
If I were to give one feedback
I should have done my makeup
a bit more
I
made the wrong choice
I went up there
with almost
no makeup on
I focused on blush and
lips and
did my eyes
a bit
lightly
But since the filter
and lighting were so strong
my eye makeup kind of got washed out?
So
I should have gone with a darker look
That was my
slight
mistake
The reason I did it like that
there's a reason for it
M Countdown
comes out
a bit dark
Normally
my eyes
can easily
look a bit stuffy
on camera
often
so
to make it
look less stuffy I removed some makeup but
unlike usual
they paid a lot of attention
really cared for it
so they used a different filter than usual
Ah
why are you asking why my mic is different?
It's not because I didn't spend money guys
It's not that I didn't buy that one
as you know I have it too. I have it
and
I have that black
mic too
I have all three mics but
why don't I use it?
I don't know if it's pretty
I mean it looks expensive
Because it is expensive
it makes sense that it looks expensive
but
to me
it's uncomfortable
That kind of mic looks like you spent money on it but
ah I find it uncomfortable
I mean because
my hair
really
when I turn my head or move
since it sticks out my hair gets wrapped around it
or it bounces in and gets caught a lot
uh
if I wear that one and try to
today
wear my hair all down. If I want to leave it down
because the mic
is worn on my ear
I want it to stick flat but
it
doesn't
like this
so
the mic
makes my hair float up
So
I can't get the hair styling I want
That part is a shame too
And I find it a bit sad
that it covers my face and
covers my lips
So I think that's why I keep using
that mic
But to keep the color
unified
I use that skin-colored
mic
Ah seeing myself makes me pop up
Should I go check out my fancam?
What am I watching right now?
What am I eating?
Supersonic fancam
Let's watch this one
This is my favorite
I looked skinny
Ah I look pretty in that should I zoom in a bit?
Ah but it is different
I was so sad about White Longing
The first broadcast
was really a shame
Because
my makeup looked so pretty in real life
But
Music Bank's lighting is a bit strong
It washes out a lot and the filter
like right now
makes you look really soft
It looks so soft
so you have to do it a bit darker
for it to look pretty. This time
I did it a bit darker
But
back then
since it was White Longing I thought I should go for an innocent look
so
um
since it was White Longing I thought I should go for an innocent look
doing it innocently
I thought it would look pretty so I did it that way
but it came out too light. The blush
all washed out too
so
it was a shame. I really liked my makeup back then though
The makeup got buried
Like
Music Bank
totally
really
requires colors like this
for it to show up
But
since I went up there with colors like this
it got washed out
It totally got washed out
Music Core
exactly
shows your makeup exactly as it is
and the makeup looks a bit clearer
It's like turning the clarity
up by 50
Just about that much
Inkigayo
shoots the lighting from below like this
so what is it?
It has a bit of
contrast
I guess you could say. Anyway Inkigayo has its own specific color tone too
M Countdown
has a huge difference between pre-recording and the live broadcast
It's quite extreme
It's different for every music show
So every single time
I have to think a lot about how to do my makeup
before going on stage
Anyway I painted my nose really red like this
red
to make it look
a bit teary-eyed
teary-eyed
teary like
I was cold and it got red
like I was about to
right about to
cry at any moment
I wanted it to look like that
so
I did my makeup that way but
it didn't get captured
It's such a shame. Let's watch one more
But honestly that outfit
is my
favorite outfit
Out of all the outfits so far
out of all
the outfits
it's my number one favorite
What is this? 150,000 people watched it?
Let's look at the Feel Good era again. Wow I was 20 back then guys. Ah
Not bad
When I look at 20-year-olds now they look like total babies
like this vibe
It's funny saying this while wearing this on my head
Back then I thought
it was really pretty but
looking at it now
it's a bit
whatever
Out of my recent
close-up face cams
I think the Music Bank one came out pretty
Today
the styling team director also
told me the Music Bank one was the prettiest
Doesn't it
remind you of that time?
But during Music Bank
Flovers'
fanchants
are the loudest
I don't know why. It's always been like that
So
I think getting curly hair was a really good choice
Originally it was just
wavy but
the hair stylist
was really satisfied with it
saying I'm satisfied
with it
The Music Bank one this time
came out pretty
Ah there are about 70 more
people there
So
that's why the cheering is the loudest
Why am I streaming for so long today? I am streaming
for a long time
Yeah
I was bored
It can get boring
Lately I've always been with the members and staff
and with my mom and dad so
being alone makes me a bit
bored
Realizing
the value of the TV license fee
I'm too lazy to get up again
How many times do I have to get up?
Ah why does it look like I'm trying to act cute? It's driving me crazy right?
I only ordered the things I like
Honeycomb
Orange
Chocolate
That's it
I'm on the cup? Where?
Ah you mean this?
Ah this is ugly
Mm
It looks so pitiful
Looks intact
Mm
I don't have muscles
Why did I put things like this here?
The oranges
why are they so sour?
You're craving sour stuff?
Yeah
I always try to
give out vitamins
so we're
eating
vitamins
We can't just keep giving them out
We have to consume them too
They should give us some
Last time I ate the Dubai
Yoajung but
that wasn't my style
For Yoajung I like it a bit more refreshing
Among our staff
there's
a young staff member
and she
did the Yaru trend
and seriously
current teens really hit different
She did it so
perfectly
I was so surprised
The members and everyone else
were like
exclamation marks popped up above our heads
so that's what Yaru is
That's Yaru
That's how it's done
It was kind of
exactly
that feeling. Wow
It's different
Kind of like that
I was so surprised. Super surprised
I don't really like how Yaru sounds either
Last time
um
Karina
unnie I think
talked about it on that show and I feel the same
somehow
the nuance
isn't really my style. But
when a current teen did it
oh
it was kind of
wow
it felt like that
But I saw they've been doing that since Infinite Challenge
Jung Hyung-don sunbaenim used to do it back in the day
There are staff members younger than Jiwon now?
There are so many people younger than me now
Realizing
the value of
the TV license fee
Ah
honestly I should have looked the prettiest on the third day
But why did I
tie my hair up?
Ah I shouldn't have tied it
The first day was the prettiest
I wonder if
the first day
was pretty without bangs?
Back then was the day I didn't have bangs
Somehow for me
somehow my
I think the second day was good
but the first day
was the face that wasn't shown fully
On the first day
I was so incredibly nervous
why was I like that?
Why did I suddenly
get so nervous?
The first day
should have been the real-time live broadcast
Such a shame
Should I just do all 3 episodes this time?
If I do
the views won't go up right?
Where was this again?
That
our
award ceremony day last year
I looked pretty that day
That day
I really liked my look that day
Waves
I'm definitely a cool tone
I really feel it lately
Ah I really am a cool tone
Whenever I wear cool
makeup or cool
clothes
I see so many people liking it
Ah
seriously
no matter how much
I claim to be a warm tone
I'm a definite cool tone
But
I didn't know
the live broadcast audio went out that well. In our in-ears
the live vocals
sounded perfectly balanced with the track and
the AR
track and
the MR and
not the track, the live vocals and
the MR
were perfectly balanced in the middle, but to you guys
on the outside
the live vocals
just overpowered the MR
and the raw voices
completely popped out like that
I was so surprised
How happy were you guys?
Looks like you ate a lot
You're curious about my algorithm?
fromis_9
A startled puppy
that anyone can see
Protect the melting ice. The era of heatwaves
2025 in Review through Songs
Ah kids
Oxygen-like guy
The fromis_9 fan meeting where you can't laugh
Full version
AI-generated
Yoo Jae-suk's
Jee Seok-jin exclusive song
60s
Jee Seok-jin reveal
Things like this
Wiggle wiggle
Lesser panda
birth
Korea's first natural breeding
And
Forest of Glass
Try calling
Air precipitation
The cat
that came to wake me up
Wasn't it just soft things living there? Stuff like this
A collection of eight summer stages you like
Looking at 2025 through songs
I've never listened to this directly but I think I heard it a lot on the streets
This is from last year
This is already
2024 and it hasn't been that long
Not this year but 2024
is what it's saying
Ah this is also a song from last year
No way
Really
that has to be a lie
I really don't suit things like this right?
Not at all
I just looked at the monitor and it was really bad
I like this song
This song
is my friend's go-to karaoke song
It's from March
How many minutes is this?
This is 30 minutes long
it's too big
You
How about this vibe?
Ah this is a bit
I shouldn't be innocent like this for this song
kind of
Uh
Ah how should I dress for this?
Today right now this isn't the vibe
Is it this vibe?
Kind of
this is so natural
do you know what vibe it is?
It's a bit
ah
At a local pub
playing a song
ah when you go to those pubs or chicken joints
the TV is super loud
playing songs like this
Having chicken
and
a glass of beer
with friends there
vibes
Suddenly
unnie came out
Ah Choi Jung-hoon
was last year
Aren't they playing recent songs?
It's not showing up here
here
But still
last year
top 5
I think it was top 5
we made it right?
We're at the flowerpot section?
That's us
We also played a big part in 2024 guys
The choreography
is confusing because I'm not doing it with my legs right?
This song is on here. Nice
Friends really
I want to do something like this. Like a band concept
If we do a song like this later would you like it?
Working so hard on it
sweat dripping
But last year was
By the way for this
I filmed a challenge with the sunbaenims before the release and
as soon as we filmed it
wow I thought this song
was going to be a hit
I only heard the challenge part
but
as soon as I saw the video
this is
going to totally blow up. That's what I thought
Blue Valentine?
So pretty
What do you think?
This is so
NewJeans
isn't it?
Total vibes
But I really don't suit these things right
You watched the ballads well
But for us now
is there nothing?
Ah
suddenly
we're on. Here
Wait
no
It's released today
I think they put our song as the ending song for us. Wait is this Flover?
They made our song the ending track
Thank you so much
In 2025 too please
include ours
The reasons why 2018 songs
were legendary
Lately
isn't this kind of vibe popular?
Or is it a bit older?
Tiger
era K-Pop
When you guys
go to karaoke
which
songs
do you listen to the most?
I perfectly
INFINITE sunbaenims
wait no
The era of
4 5 6 7
This
I suddenly wish winter would come
Suddenly I miss winter
Know why?
Because this song popped up right in front of me
This song popped up
But dancing to that in this outfit really
doesn't match
I really grew up so fast
But to hide it a bit
no matter how much I try
I can't become young again
If I make a mistake now
winking and sticking my tongue out
is really
intense timing
Everyone
we did looking back at 2024 through songs
I actually like 2024 songs
more than I thought
What
hey there
this is really you
I really like it
so much it hurts
Actually when I
go to Inkigayo
I kind of
thought of the outfit from Smart so I tried to learn it
and dance to it but
I learned it
I had time to learn it
Ah Queen of Tears
This is
comfort
There are a lot of masterpieces in 2024
Ah this kind of gives beer commercial vibes
but I don't like beer
Ah
I'm fermenting
Ah I'm being too careful
Ah I really love this song
Ddu-du
isn't it embarrassing
All of NewJeans' songs are good
But aren't we coming out?
So
I remember
I have to listen to this
It's coming on
It's Hayoung unnie. Must be her favorite
Sometimes
Super
Ah
when I hear the intro to Supersonic
right before the stage when the intro plays
the intro on stage
when I hear it
I get goosebumps
During the Supersonic intro
strangely
there are times like that out of nowhere
It's good of course but suddenly at that moment
I remember the atmosphere back then
before we did Supersonic
all the
staff members and
the members all
felt like
Ah I have a good feeling about this. We had that going on. So
even during practice
somehow
we were able to work really hard because
we just kept having a good feeling
During practice too
so
my body
was really
exhausted
because the choreo was so
intense it was really tough but
during
preparation
my mind wasn't exhausted at all
not at all
and I wasn't even worried
That kind of album
Somehow
it wasn't about the pressure of chart results or anything. Just completely
none of that
The feeling
felt easy and
somehow
I think the thought of I should just have fun was really strong
Somehow
truly
out of all the albums
the time we cared the least about the results was Supersonic
It's fine
Fun
karaoke
No I'm telling you guys not to sing
playlist
Karaoke popular chart
Yes
It broke
When a Man
Loves
It's a masterpiece
If you sing this at karaoke
doesn't everyone sing along?
My
friends
the lyrics are so cute
Up to what birth year
would people know this song?
Do you know it?
Ah 2004 liners definitely know it
I know it so
1979 liners
If you're a 2012 liner
you don't know it
You need to go study some history. This
song
kind of
flows
Since I'm dressed like this
I look a bit like those scary unnies
you know what I mean?
Don't you think?
Kind of like the unnies
who were always hanging out at the coin karaoke
The unnies who basically lived there
Wearing a school uniform skirt below
Unnies
Kind of this vibe this vibe this vibe
Kind of
middle school
Has to be a middle schooler
Yeah a student with this vibe
Has to look something like this
I'll go back to my middle school days
Let's do that
I actually dropped out though
I was in disguise and then dropped out
In elementary school
I was the school president
I was the student council president
I never missed out
on being class president or vice president. Yeah
Yeah
Do you know this today?
The lyrics are a bit
I used to sing it without knowing the meaning at all
Those days
right
The lyrics are too
bad
Wow
Is this a CUBE song?
This is
I can't handle this guys
This is history I tell you
Study your history
Do it when I'm teaching you like this
Don't you know?
But there might be some people who don't know it
I also heard this when I was close with them I think
When I listen
to this song
I think of exactly when I was 15
back when I was doing the survival program
and they just
kept playing this song
Memories
Right
Ah I like it
It's been 10 years since this
This was when I was 14
exactly 10 years ago
How old was I?
Why do I know all these songs so well?
Me
That this is the end
how could this song
be like that?
This is basically like a song that just came out yesterday
Ah I really like the sunbaenims
I don't have
a single song I don't like
Just from watching a lot
It's ET
No it isn't
Ah what animal is it?
Ah but our young Flovers probably won't know this song at all
Because even I've never seen this performed on stage
I
as someone from the late era
only found out about it after I became a fan
I also like f(x) sunbaenims
I think I have candy
I washed this
Do people usually listen to it like this?
Today I'm listening to it like this with my friends
Here
like the old days
friends I used to go to karaoke with
because we're friends
out of my friends always
not looking like this. Just looking a bit ugly like this
just every week like this
Touching
It's hard
I don't know this one
I was preparing from before and
I should be preparing
I'm EXO's
true fan
Originally
Flover
Normally I
Oh my
that startled me
Wow
Surprised
The vibe I originally wanted to show
I'll show you
Wait a second
I need to put on more lip tint
My lips
need to be redder
for it to work
You probably can't see it from here but
you really can't see it
Anyway I'll show you
I never planned on having bangs originally
Flovers like them so
I kept them but
the vibe I originally had in mind
was kind of like this
Chic
vibe
First I want to
blow my hair back like this
Whoosh
Ah this kind of thing
Yeah
Now
kind of this
neglected
that kind of vibe
Later on I'll
dance with the vibes I imagined
I
asked for it
Since I cut my hair
I look cooler now so
it doesn't give off a baby vibe
Anyway
when I was doing that
I really only thought I messed up
I didn't know where it went
Because
back then I had fake nails on
and when I tried to flick my hair
it got caught right here
So
I kind of yanked it out and
while doing it
you could slightly see
a bit of
genuine annoyance
coming out
So
honestly
I did it exactly like this but
I'm probably ripping it out
I yanked it out
That
shows
I lifted it up but it wouldn't go in
like this
Unnie really suits English
Wow
You're kidding
I can only see Seoyeon right now
Wow
Let's wrap this up
Ah I really played hard
today
I'm so exhausted
Ah it was really fun
Ah
Wrap it up. Let's finish
I'm going to go
take off my makeup now
Bye
Bye. Bye. I need to clean this up. When am I going to clean it? Ah. Ah
Thanks for hanging out with me